Sardorjon Mirzakarimov

Software and Web Developer

Graduated in the field of Computer Sciences (Software Engineering) with a good knowledge of IT skills such as C, C++, Java Python programming languages, HTML, HTML5, CSS, PHP, and JavaScript Web application languages as well as MySQL Database Management system. Gained experience in analyzing and solving the problems related to software and web systems. Experienced in real life software and web system design and development. Able to use variety of electronic devices and understand basic concepts and techniques. Accomplished in generating and implementing new algorithms.





sardor_kb@outlook.com



+96897834777



Al Buraimi, Sultanate of Oman

EDUCATION

Software Engineering

University Malaysia Sarawak

02/2016 - 07/2021

Accounting and Audit

Kokand Service and Business Vocational College

09/2011 - 06/2014

WORK EXPERIENCE

Branch manager & Web admin

Tayr Al Ymamt Trading SPC

Al Buraimi, Sultanate of Oman Tayr Al Ymamt is a family-owned company specialized in import, export and sale of veterinary medicines and tools located in Sultanate of Oman.

- Manage resources and staff developing and attaining sales goals.
- Develop and implement e-commerce web system and manage.
- Manage all social media accounts.

Web admin & Cashier Peridot Kuchina

07/2019 - 10/2020

Kuching, Malaysia

Peridot Western Restaurant located in Kuching city of Malaysia is well-equipped to cater for all types of events.

- Processing and receiving payments and issuing receipts to
- Manage, keep web page content and links up to date, find and fix web page problems.

Software Engineering Intern

University Malaysia Sarawak

02/2019 - 07/2019

Kota Samarahan, Malaysia

University Malaysia Sarawak. The Faculty of Computer Science and Information Technology, also known as FCSIT, was established in 1992.

- Research in text similarities using variety of algorithms.
- Implement variety of algorithms into the web system using PHP scripting language.
- Develop web system that tests the text similarities in malay language.

Web Developer

360 Degree Creative Agency

03/2018 - 01/2019 Kuching, Malaysia

Consulting agency specialized in consulting, developing and marketing new businesses with the help of modern technology.

Achievements/Tasks

- Develop web systems built using frameworks Django, Laravel, and
- Assist in creating and managing shopify accounts

PERSONAL SKILLS

High level of integrity and moral standards.

Excellent interpersonal, networking and presentation.

Able to express myself appropriately using a variety of methods and be understood by others.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Arabia Experience Web System (08/2022 - Present)

Develop a web-based system for one of the leading language centre in the Sultanate of Oman.

FrenchPharm FZC Web System (07/2021 - 11/2021)

Develop a web-based system for Private Limited Company in Sharjah, United Arab Emirates.

Web-based Grading and Monitoring System for Primary School (01/2020 - 05/2020)

The scope of the project aims to allow the primary school to manage and track pupil's grades through a web-based system.

LANGUAGES

Uzbek

Native or Bilinaual Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Professional Working Proficiency

Malay Elementary Proficiency Professional Working Proficiency

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

C, C++, Java and Python Programming languages.

HTML, CSS and PHP Web Application languages. JavaScript and its libraries. MySQL Database Management system.

Diango and Laravel Web Frameworks.

Microsoft 365 Apps.

Ability to use a variety of software.